你的咖啡 谢谢
-Here you go. -Thank you.
瑞秋
"Say,Rachel...
有空要不要一起去看电影…
...I was wondering if you'd go to a movie with me sometime...
以情侣的身份
...as my lover."
太明显了
Too out there.
改天要不要一起吃饭…
"Maybe you'd like to have dinner with me sometime...
以情侣的身份
...as my lover."
好，买东西去
All right,let's go shopping.
我的信用卡收入大于支出，我想在花旗银行破产之前使用它
l got a positive balance on my credit card l want to use before Citibank goes under.
好主意，好主意
Good idea. Good idea.
走之前我有话要说
Before we go,there's something I need to say.
我很喜欢你
I've kind of had this crush on you.
以前有罗斯，我不方便行动
Since you were with Ross,I didn't do anything about it.
既然你们分手，我想约你出去
Now that you're not,I'd really like to ask you out sometime.
我现在就是在…
So that's what I'm doing...
约你
... now.
我掉了一个杯子
I dropped a cup.
本集播出：“小T恤”
The One With the Tiny T-Shirt
再过几年，语音辨识系统
So within a few years,voice recognition...
将成为电脑基本配备
...will be standard on any computer.
你可以说“去洗车” “去打扫房间”
You know,so you could be,like,"Wash my car." "Clean my room."
电脑办不到，但是听得懂
It won't be able to do any of those things,but it'll understand.
哇哦，如果我这样讲话的话 它能辨别出我的声音吗
Wow. Would it be able to recognize my voice if l talked like this?
是的，会懂你的意思，但是也会取笑你
Oh, yeah. lt'll understand you,but it's gonna make fun of you.
好棒喔
Oh,this was so great.
是啊
Yeah,it was.
就这样吧
All right,then.
再见
Bye.
嗨，不住在这里的人
Hello,people who do not live here.
备用钥匙是有急事时用的
I gave you a key for emergencies.
我们没有多力多滋了（薯片品牌）
We were out of Doritos.
跟百万富翁的约会如何？
Hey,how'd the date go with Mr. Millionaire?
“百万富翁先生” 傲慢玩具最新出品
"Mr. Millionaire. New,from Snooty Playthings.
三老婆单独发售
Third wife sold separately."
他很棒，我们在一起很开心
He's great. We have such a good time together.
他风趣又体帖 而我对他没兴趣
He's so funny and so sweet. And I'm not attracted to him at all!
还是没兴趣？
Still?
我快疯了 他在各方面都很完美
It's driving me crazy. In every other way,he's the perfect guy.
他什么都好，而且什么都有
He has everything. Plus,he actually has everything.
有“醒目形象”（美国最大零售商）出品的 真人大小的“帝国风暴战士”（《星球大战》）吗？
Life-sized lmperial Storm Troopers from Sharper lmage?
两套
Two.
乔伊和我可以拿来对打吗？
Can Joey and I put them on and fight?
老妈，老爸，我是超级坏小子
Oh,Mommy! Oh,Daddy! I am a big old baddy
他一定得到那出舞台剧了
I guess he must've gotten the part in that play.
或正如葛萝莉亚伊丝特芬（拉丁歌后）所唱
Either that,or Gloria Estefan was right.
人迟早会随节奏起舞（歌名）
Eventually,the rhythm is going to get you.
乔，你好吗？ 很好
-Joe,how's it going? -Good.
你演艾德莉恩？
So you're playing Adrianne?
对，你演智障堂哥？
Yes. Are you one of the retarded cousins?
不是，我演你的丈夫维克多 乔伊崔比亚尼
No. I'm playing your husband,Victor. I'm Joey Tribbiani.
很高兴认识你，凯特米勒
Hi. Nice to meet you. Kate Miller.
这个剧本很棒吧？
So the play's pretty great,huh?
是啊，我好喜欢 珍妮佛班贝利的作品
Oh,yeah. I love Jennifer Banberry's work.
她尤其能精确的解构中产阶级
She's so incisive when it comes to deconstructing the middle class.
不用多说，她超厉害
Oh,forget about it. She rocks!
我在哪里见过你？
Where do I know you from?
德瑞克雷莫瑞医生？
Dr. Drake Ramoray?
“我们的日子”？
Days of our Lives?
“少女杂志”票选为 最想跟他约会的神经外科医生
Voted most datable neurosurgeon by Teen Beat?.
不是那个
No,that's not it.
原来你是连续剧演员
So you're a soap actor.
能演出舞台剧，你一定很兴奋
This must be exciting for you,being in a real play.
我也演过舞台剧 我是正剧演员
Hey,I've done plays before. I'm a serious actor.
那支公益广告
That infomercial!
倒盒装牛奶那一支
For the milk-carton-spout thing!
你是那个不会倒牛奶的人
You're the guy who doesn't know how to pour milk!
我会倒牛奶，我把你骗倒了
I actually can pour milk. But I got you believing that I couldn't.
这就是演技
Now,see,that's acting.
你还被饼干噎到
Right. At the end,you choked on a cookie.
那是真的
That was real.
马克居然约你出去 是啊
-I cannot believe Mark asked you out. -I know.
你要怎么回答？
What are you gonna tell him?
我说我会考虑，但是我要拒绝
I told him I would think about it,but I'm gonna tell him no.
我目前不想约会
I think I'd say no to anybody right now.
好奇怪，这样一个…
But it was so strange. I mean,I'm standing there...
迷人、英俊的男人约我出去
...with this charming,cute guy who's asking me to go out with him...
而我也可以去
...which I'm allowed to do...
但我却有罪恶感 仿佛那样是背叛罗斯
...and I felt guilty,like I'd be cheating on Ross or something.
也许这代表…
Wow. So,okay,maybe that means...
你还没有忘情罗斯 而且有父女问题
...you're not over Ross yet and you have issues with your father.
我没有父女问题 那就是罗斯的问题了
-I don't have issues with my father. -So it's just the Ross thing.
我恨这个女人，我恨她
I hate this woman! I hate her!
她到处宣传公益广告的事
She told everyone about that infomercial...
大家都跑来找我开饮料
...and now they all keep asking me to open their drinks!
每次我打不开，他们就笑我
And whenever I can't do it,they're all,like,laughing at me!
瑞秋打电话来
So Rachel called.
说想见我
Wants to see me.
我待会儿就要过去
Going over in a minute.
你觉得她有什么事？ 也许是疯狂的烟雾已经消散
-What do you think she wants? -Maybe the crazy fog has lifted...
发现没有我的人生…
...and she realizes that life without me...
是糟糕的
...sucks.
有可能，你很可爱 要是我跟你分手，也会想念你
It's possible. You are very lovable. I'd miss you if I broke up with you.
我想表达支持
Just trying to be supportive.
请以男人的方式表达
Be supportive like a guy.
要是我跟你分手，也会想念你
If I broke up with you,I'd miss you.
你想见我？
You wanted to see me?
这一盒是你的东西
Here's a box of your stuff.
就是帽子、衣服、CD 一些你留在这里的东西
It's just hats and a shirt and CD's. Just stuff that you've left here.
你干什么？想伤害我？
What are you doing? Are you trying to hurt me or something?
我只是觉得我们该往前走了
It just seems that,you know,it's time we move on.
你不同意吗？
I mean,don't you think?
同意啊 那就好
-Yes,I do. -Good.
我真的同意
I really do.
这是我送你的
This was a gift.
那是博物馆礼品部的赠品
You got that for free from the museum gift shop.
它一样是礼物
It's still a gift.
我是从“礼品部”拿到的
I got it from the "gift" shop.
好，给我，我留着就是了
Okay! All right! Give me the mug! I'll keep the mug!
不必假好心
Don't do me any favors.
既然如此…
In fact...
其他的东西呢？像…
...where's the rest of my stuff? Like my....
这本书是我的
This book is mine!
你当成睡衣穿的T恤呢？ 我要拿回来 没错
And that T-shirt you sleep in? I'd like that back too. Yes,I do.
你明知我很喜欢那件衣服 你根本没在穿
You know how much I love that T-shirt. You never even wear that T-shirt.
我是在帮你往前走
I'm just trying to help you "move on."
你真小器
Oh,you are a petty man.
小器…
You are a petty,petty...
-Petty... -... petty,petty...
小心眼…
-...small.... -...small....
你是故意要气我的
You are so just doing this out of spite.
我会一直穿着，我爱这件衣服
I'm gonna wear this all the time! I love this shirt!
你15岁之后就没穿过了 根本塞不下
You haven't worn it since you were 15! It doesn't even fit you anymore!
（法兰基说：放轻松）
不好意思，我要把东西拿走了
If you don't mind,I'm gonna take the rest of my stuff...
我要去放轻松…
...and "relax"...
穿着我最爱的衣服
...in my favorite shirt.
祝你今晚愉快
You have a pleasant evening.
你是亿兆富翁
So you're,like,a zillionaire.
却跟我们差不多大的年纪
And you're our age. You're our age.
你知道吗？你应该买下一个州
You know what? You should buy a state...
取你自己的名字
...and then just name it after yourself.
例如彼达科塔？
Like,"Pete Dakota"?
或是密西西彼特
Or "Mississi-Pete."
我知道了：彼芝加哥
I got it: "Pete Chicago."
芝加哥不是州
That's not a state,Joe.
密西西彼特就是？
Oh,and "Mississi-Pete" is?
我该走了
I gotta go.
改天见
I'll see you guys later.
你跟我们差不多大的年纪
You're our age.
明天再见？
So are we on for tomorrow?
好
Absolutely.
快走吧你
Now,get out of here,you!
我快要没地方可以摸了
Okay,I'm running out of places I can touch him.
我有毛病吗？
Is something wrong with me?
我为何总是喜欢没有未来的人
Why am I only attracted to guys with no future?
不是太老，就是太小
Either they're too old,or they're too young.
或者是不尊重妇女的混蛋诗人比如胡里欧
Or they're a big misogynist jerk poet like Julio.
顺便说一下，我还对他有感觉
Who, by the way, l'm still attracted to.
彼特这么喜欢我
And there's Pete,who's crazy about me...
而且这么完美，我们又合得来
...and he's absolutely perfect,and there's zip going on!
我是不是有什么毛病？
Does it sound like something's wrong with me?
好像是
Yeah,kind of.
我应该感到开心吗？
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be,Vic?
是吗？
Happy?
不如由你来告诉我
Why don't you tell me what you're supposed to be?
因为我实在搞不懂
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out!
我们的交谈没有感情
I talk to you,and nothing!
你看着我的眼神没有感情
You look at me,and it's nothing!
什么都没有
Nothing.
有意思
Tasty.
我开始觉得 你们有渊源了，很好
I'm really starting to feel like you guys have a history. It's nice.
我对这场戏有个疑问
I have a question about this scene.
艾德莉恩为什么会喜欢维克多？
I don't understand why Adrianne's attracted to Victor.
你要拨开洋葱皮
Peel the onion.
第一，他很帅
First of all,he's good-looking.
我的角色需要更好的理由
My character needs a bit more of a reason than that.
这样行不行，因为剧本这么写！
Hey,how about this one? It says so in the script!
我也不知道维克多为什么喜欢你
I don't know why my character likes you either.
剧本上说你是个贱人
I mean,it says in the script that you're a bitch.
剧本上没写 我这一本有
-lt doesn't say that in the script. -lt does in mine.
我吹干、上发胶，还是一样
I can blow-dry it,gel it. It doesn't matter.
还是有一撮…
I still wind up with this little...
像是被牛舔过的头发，烦死了
...cowlick-y thing on the middle part of my head. It's so annoying.
-你看了烦不烦？ -你比较烦
-Does it bug you? -You bug me.
你会不会刚好没看到？
Is there any chance you didn't see that?
罗斯，别再看了
Ross,you gotta stop,okay?
你不能在那里瞄上三小时
You can't stare through the peephole for three hours.
你会得偷窥眼
You're gonna get peep-eye.
我就知道，我就知道她喜欢他
I knew it. I knew it. I always knew she liked him.
她一直否认，结果呢 我们才刚分手，她就这么做了
She'd say no,but here we are. We just broke up,first thing she does!
你们没有“才刚分手”
You didn't "just break up."
才三个星期
It's been,like,three weeks!
你不到三小时就跟别人上床
You slept with somebody three hours after you thought you broke up.
连子弹都没这么快
I mean,bullets have left guns slower.
他们回来了…
Here they come! Here they
要是她跟他吻别，我会自杀
If she kisses him good night,I'll kill myself.
我看不下去了
I can't watch.
约会该结束了
Come on. Date over! Date over!
没事，她要进去了
Here we go. She's going in.
她要进去了
She's going in.
他也要进去
Wait! He's going in!
他进去了
He's going in!
门关了，门关着我看不到
The door's closed! I can't see anything with the door closed!
门的发明者可以安息了
And the inventor of the door rests happily in his grave.
我得想办法阻止
I have to do something. I have to stop it!
阻止什么？ 我不知道
-Stop what? -I don't know.
但只要我过去就行了
But I have a feeling my being there will do it.
看，这家伙是个坏消息，钱德， 我能感觉他是个精明的人（有“操作工”的意思）
Look, this guy is bad news, Chandler.l can sense he's an operator.
瑞秋不会跟操作工约会的
Rachel wouldn't date an operator.
他们一年只挣两万块，并且晚上也要工作
They only make 20 grand a year and they have to work nights.
我要过去借东西
I'll go over and I will borrow something!
果汁！我要喝果汁
Juice! I need juice!
不行
You can't!
一定要阻止他们 我是你的朋友
-They must be stopped! -I am your friend...
我不会让你这么做
...and I won't let you do this!
你还真强壮
You are surprisingly strong!
我要喝果汁，人都要喝果汁 听我说
-I need juice! People need juice! -Look,man....
人都要喝果汁 听我说！
-People need juice! -Listen to me!
她往前走了 就算不是他，也会有别人
She's moving on. If it's not this guy,it's gonna be somebody else.
除非你打算租下这个窥视孔
And unless you're thinking about subletting my peephole...
否则你就得面对分手的事实
...you'll have to get used to the fact that it's over!
好吗？结束了
Okay,man? It's over.
我真的很想她
It's just I miss her so much.
我知道
I know.
只是我这么想，还是说“租下我的偷窥孔”确实听起来很色？
ls it just me, or did ''subletting my peephole'' sound kind of dirty?
咖啡杯为什么有编号？
Why do your coffee mugs have numbers?
这样莫妮卡才方便追踪
Oh,that's so Monica can keep track.
要是少了一个 她就可以说27号杯呢？
So if one of them's missing,she can be like,"Where's number 27?"
你知道吗？
You know what?
不知道，也不想知道
No,and I don't think I'm gonna want to.
我办不到 我就是不想知道这件事
-I can't do this. -That's what I didn't want to know.
我的出发点是错的
Oh,I'm just doing this for the wrong reasons,you know?
我只是想报复罗斯
I'm doing it to get back at Ross.
对不起，这样对你不公平
I'm sorry. It's not very fair to you.
去他的公平
Fair,shmair. You know?
你想报复罗斯，尽管找我
You wanna get back at Ross,I am here for you.
真的
Really.
我们就在这张沙发上报复他吧
I say we get back at him right here on this couch. Right here!
天哪
Oh,my God.
很抱歉
I'm sorry about this.
没关系
That's okay.
你确定？
You sure?
我可以回家自己报复他
I can just go home and get back at him by myself.
将成为21世纪的青霉素
and should become the penicillin of the 2 1st century.
所以今天，本院将朝领导改革
And so today,this hospital is about to take major steps...
跨出一大步
...toward leading that revolution.
问你一件事
Can I ask you something?
我们在哪里？
Where are we?
有这么多医生、护士在场
Well,with all these doctors and nurses...
应该是小型马术表演
... I'm gonna say,"Midget Rodeo."
跟我说实话
Just tell me the truth.
我应该没有告诉你
You know,I don't think I told you this...
我刚结束一段很认真的感情
... but I just recently got out of a serious relationship.
一年前对吧？
Oh,right. Wasn't that a year ago?
原来我说过了
So I did tell you.
其实不是这个原因
That's not really the thing.
我目前想把注意力 放在自己身上
I'm just in a place in my life where I need to focus on me.
你懂吗？ 我懂
-Do you know what I mean? -Oh,I know.
-我也想对你有兴趣 -但是你没有，好
-I so want to be attracted to you. -But you're not. Okay. Good.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不必对不起
You know what? Don't be.
真的，没有那么糟
Don't be,because it's not so bad.
真的？
It's not?
我又不是约翰邦乔维（最有影响力的流行摇滚歌手）
Yeah. I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
或是什么有魅力的人
Or someone you find attractive.
我只是觉得…
I just think,you know...
你的感觉或许会变
...that you might end up feeling differently.
你别误会
I don't want this to come out wrong...
但是以被拒绝的人来说 你还真有自信
...but you're awfully confident for a guy I said I wasn't attracted to.
傻得很可爱吧？
Stupidly charming,isn't it?
要不要去吃饭？ 这里蛮令人沮丧的
You wanna get something to eat? This place is kind of depressing.
我们欢迎促成这件事的功臣 彼特贝克先生
Now the man who made all of this possible,Mr. Peter Becker.
等一下
One second.
我不认为这个镇足够大 可以让我们两个在这里休息
I don't think this town is big enough for the both of us to relax in.
拔枪！
Draw!
我什么也没做
I wasn't doing anything.
她又怎么了？
What did she do now?
仅仅因为她来自耶鲁戏剧学院 就认为自己是最伟大的女演员
Just because she went to Yale,she thinks she's the greatest actress...
自从有了切片面包以来？（俚语，表示“有史以来”）
...since sliced bread.
切片面包 真是伟大的麦克白夫人（莎士比亚戏剧《麦克白》中的恶妇）
Ah,Sliced Bread. A wonderful Lady Macbeth.
我恨她，我恨她的 “我好有才华”
I hate her. I hate her with her "Oh,I'm so talented"...
“我好漂亮”、“我好香”
...and "Oh,I'm so pretty," and "Oh,I smell so good."
有某人喜欢上某人
I think somebody has a crush on somebody.
请专心讨论我的问题好吗？
Can we please try and stay focused on my problem here?
我就是说你，你这个怪人
I'm talking about you,you big,big freak.
少来了
You're out of your mind!
这48小时以来你开口闭口都是她
You've done nothing but talk about her for 48 hours.
要是在学校里你已经 在拉她的辫子、把她推倒在地了
If you were in school,you'd be pulling her pigtails and pushing her down now.
那为什么我老是想着…
Then how come I keep thinking about her...
要用各种姿势跟她做爱？
...in all these sexual scenarios and stuff?
我应该感到开心，是吗？
Happy? Is that what I'm supposed to be,Vic? Happy?
不如由你来告诉我
Why don't you tell me what you're supposed to be,huh?
因为我实在搞不懂
Because I sure as hell can't figure it out.
我们的交谈没有感情
I talk to you,and it's nothing.
你看着我的眼神没有感情
You look at me,and nothing.
什么都没有
Nothing.
你们让我爽翻天了
You guys make me fly!
爽死了
High!
明天再继续排
Okay,we're gonna pick it up here,tomorrow.
刚才… 好多了？
-Well,that was.... -Better?
对，的确…
Yeah,it was definitely...
有进步
...an improvement.
再见 凯特
-Good night. -Kate.
你忘了拿鞋子
You forgot your shoes.
不穿鞋子恐怕不行
I'm probably gonna need those,huh?
凯特
Hey,listen...
要不要去喝杯咖啡？
...you feel like getting a cup of coffee?
凯特
Kate...
可以走了吗？
...you ready to go?
很好，非常好
Very nice. Very nice.
明天见 好
-See you tomorrow? -Yeah. Sure.
再见 晚安
-Right. -Good night.
为什么没有蜘蛛人？
Why isn't it "Spiderman"?
像是金人、银人
Like Goldman,Silverman?
因为那不是他的姓
Because it's not his last name.
不是吗？
It isn't?
他又不叫…
It's not,like...
菲尔蜘蛛人
... Phil Spiderman.
他是个蜘蛛…
He's a Spider-...
人
... man.
像金人是姓氏
You know,like,Goldman is a last name.
但是没有金色的人
But there's no Gold Man.
应该会有金色的人
There should be a Gold Man!
工作顺利吗？ 很好
-How was work? -Oh,great.
不过我不小心坐到了地上
Although I did sit down where there wasn't a chair.
罗斯拿了一盒你的东西来
By the way,Ross dropped by a box of your stuff.
意料中的事
Oh. Well,I guess I had that one coming.
直接扔掉吧，还不是洗发水或者…
I'm just gonna throw it out. It's probably just shampoo and
怎么了？
Something wrong?
没事
No. Nothing.
金人有什么超能力？
So what kind of powers would "Gold Man" have?
他能把东西变成金子
Okay. Well,he would turn things to gold.
已经是金子的东西呢？ 那就是完成任务了
-And things that are already gold? -His work is done.
我有一个朋友叫吉米塔伯（有“保鲜”的含义） 他有什么能力？
Okay, l have a friend, Jimmy Tupperman,what would his powers be?
保鲜人
Tupper Man.
他会保持罪犯新鲜直到警察赶来
He would keep criminals fresh until the police came.
来玩我的游戏
Let's play my game.
你这个黄色有肚子的，穿制服下垂的…
All right,you yellow-bellied,lily-livered
拔枪！
Draw!